Destiny. Fate. Dreams.
These unstoppable ideals are
held deep in the heart of man.
As long as there are people
who seek freedom in this life,
these things shall not
vanish from the earth.
People tell me my head's in the clouds.
I don't care what they say
because I'm dreaming of you.
You are the treasure I found.
So bright, so bold, it's so elusive.
It's hard to look away.
Even though it's blinding me.
There are no words to
describe how I feel inside.
I'm really, really stuck on you.
I have to follow my dreams,
however crazy they seem.
And I won't stop till I
get there, you will see.
You're all I need to have
the strength to believe.
Believe in wonderland.
I'm gonna follow my dreams,
however crazy they seem.
I'm gonna share them
with you, a love so true.
You're all I want,
together we can move on.
We live how we want to.
There is no limit to us.
We have the power of love.
We don't want to live ordinary life.
We have a chance to live in paradise.
We believe in one another.
Well, Straw Hat Luffy,
this is a good way to die.
Within six minutes, this yard will
be blown up along with the square.
I'd stay, but I'm in a hurry.
You just wait right there, okay?
And then you can celebrate the
new king of the sand country.
Now then.
I should be on my way.
He said it's in the Mortuary
Temple to the west of here.
Missed me.
That was way too close!
That bastard!
He took off!
I think he flew off in that direction.
He won't get away with this!
Damn him!
So this is the royal tomb,
where generations of your kings
lay in their eternal rest.
So, where's the Poneglyph?
Hidden Stairs
The Poneglyph is kept down
there, deep underground
Most people aren't even aware
of the Poneglyph's existence
Many events occur behind the
scenes Just because a country
belongs to the world government
Doesn't necessarily mean
that its king knows what's
going on You shouldn't be blamed
Like most people,
you probably had no idea
there was someone left
in the world who can
decipher the ancient writing.
You can actually read poneglyphs?
That's right.
That's why Crocodile and I ended
up as a team in the first place.
It's also why he can't kill me.
I'm no use dead.
Tell me, is it correct that the poneglyph
in this country tells where Pluton is?
Is that really the case?
Alabasta's royal family has been obligated
for generations now to protect it.
That duty is about the only thing we
know about it protect don't make me laugh
This place is quite impressive.
It's located behind the doors in the back
There it is
This way!
Now you died!
What are you doing?
What am I doing?
I'm trying to get inside
Crocodile's head, that's what!
Like if I were him, where would
I want to shoot a cannon from?
Just keep looking!
We only have five minutes!
Five minutes to go before
a million people all die!
We really need to hurry!
We don't have much time
left to find the cannon!
Chopper, do you think you can
find the guy by using your nose?
That won't work.
The only thing I can smell
anywhere is gunpowder.
We have to do something!
Try finding the smell of a guy who's about
to blow up the square with a big cannon!
What kind of smell is that?
How should I know?
Just try it!
A cannonball that can
blow up that big an area?
Hold on.
In that case, it's gotta be really big.
And if it's gonna be shot out of a
cannon, it surely can't go very far.
So it's gotta be closer
to the square than this!
Ah!
There's no way I have time to go around!
There, a shortcut!
Anything from the sky, Pell?
I searched every rooftop near the square,
but I couldn't see any sign of a cannon.
Well, then, it might be
in a building somewhere.
Right, I'll search them all.
Good!
How many times must you
try this before giving up?
Crocodile, it's you.
Looks like Nico Robin
made short work of you.
I must say, I never thought the
Marines would follow me to the city.
Where's your boss?
Did that smoky idiot run
away and leave you all alone?
Justice is only for
the people who take it.
That's the kind of world we live in, girl.
Why don't you just go back
to your base and talk about
justice until you're actually
ready to fight for it?
Crocodile!
crocodile Straw Hat where'd he go where
tell me right now which way did he go
Towards the temple. That way.
That direction! Thank you!
What justice is there?
To hell with Marine Headquarters.
Jeez, I can't move very well.
This is strange.
I ate all that meat.
What's wrong?
These wounds are small.
I wonder if I should lie down.
Well, did it tell you everything
that you wanted to know?
Now I see it.
Secret stairs.
Just four more minutes!
Aren't there any others around?
Is this all that your country is hiding?
You aren't satisfied?
I have kept every word of
the promise I made to you.
You did.
Just like any other national secret.
No matter how hard you look, you can't find
it unless you already know where it is.
So, this is the Poneglyph
we were looking for.
That didn't take much time.
Now that you have this odd thing in front
of you, were you able to decipher it?
Yes. Very good.
Now, read it aloud.
What does this thing say?
Kahira conquered Alabasta.
In Sky Ephemeris, year 239.
In year 260, Tamer
ruled the Baton dynasty.
In year 306, the Taf Cathedral
was completed in Aramalu.
In year 325, the hero Mamden
of... Hey, hold on! What's this?
Is this really all the information here?
I don't give a damn about
this desert's history.
I want to know about the
world's most dangerous
military power that's
hiding in this country.
Where is the Pluton hidden?
That information isn't on here. What?
History is the only thing
that this text contains.
That's all? Pluton.
I didn't see it anywhere.
It isn't mentioned on
this poneglyph at all.
Not mentioned at all, I see.
That's unfortunate.
You've been an excellent
partner, but even so,
I think that I'll kill you right here.
What?
The agreement that we made four
years ago has been fulfilled.
Do you remember the
terms of that agreement?
I was to bring you to the
Poneglyph, and in turn,
you would hand over the
information on the weapon to me.
The work you've done for Baroque
Works these past four years was
excellent both in terms of intellect
and your ability to command.
Your usefulness to the company has
been reason enough to keep you around.
But in the end, you've spoiled it all.
By betraying me, Nico Robin!
You say the poneglyph in this country
doesn't say anything at all about Pluton.
Is that true? You?
Was this the plan all along to
hide the information from me,
even if you were able to
find something useful?
But even so, I don't feel
any anger toward you.
And do you know why that is, Nico Robin?
Huh. All right.
I've worked with you for four years.
I knew you'd try something like this
someday, so I'm more than ready.
One!
If you get wet, then a knife
should go right into you!
Damn it! Where'd he go?
Now all is forgiven, Nico Robin.
Because I never trusted you from the
very beginning of our partnership.
I knew better than to do
something as foolish as that.
I can tell from Cobra's reaction
that Pluton really does exist.
I don't need the Poneglyph.
I can find the Pluton on my own.
Once this country is mine,
it's only a matter of time.
What's happening?
It's still too early for
the attack on the square.
It must be you. What did you do?
It's just a little present.
You see,
this underground temple was built so
that disturbing just one small column
will destroy the balance of the entire
structure and cause it to collapse.
The two of you are going to die here.
We'll meet death together.
I am the Twelfth King
of the Nefertari family.
I will uphold our honor.
Someone like you can never be
allowed to rule the Desert Kingdom.
Impressive.
You truly are a model king, willing to
give your own life just to take me down
with you for your kingdom.
Except I won't die.
All I have to do is
change the rocks to sand
and I can escape from here.
Your death will be in vain, Cobra.
There are only three
minutes Left when the square
blows up and this temple
collapses everyone standing
in my way will be eliminated
in an instant and in
that moment this land
will become mine entirely?
Three minutes left
where is it a cannon big
enough to destroy such
a large area has to be
enormous there can't be
many places to hide such
a weapon so why are we
still unable to find it?
But after all this, open space
where a cannon would fit.
Stop shooting!
Open space.
That's not fair, Koza.
Hiding in a place like
this the entire time?
Yeah, leader, no fair!
Yes, that place would work.
That's dangerous!
I told you to stop shooting at me!
Hey, smoke shark!
It's perfect.
It's hidden and it's big.
Stop it, idiot!
I told you I'm not from the Rebel Army!
Hey, Usopp hammer, Usopp
rubber, that's your teacher.
Do they know who they're
dealing with here?
Don't be afraid when I tell you this.
No, be very afraid.
I am the incredible Captain Usopp.
What?
Oh, it's you, Vivi.
So were you able to find the cannon here?
I know now.
I figured it out. What?
You know where?
There it is.
I'll go ahead and signal everyone.
You're sure about this, right?
Special attack.
Red surface.
Let's go!
I slept good. Wait.
Oh, that's right.
I couldn't move all of a sudden,
so I decided to risk
it and take a nap right
here since there was
really no other choice.
Yeah, and I feel better now. So...
Time for me to beat up Crocodile!
That hole over there looks kind of...
kind of crockish.
It's with this freaky place anyway.
The whole thing is crumbling into pieces.
I'm certain of it.
The cannon has to be in there.
I can't think of any other
options besides that place.
What makes you so sure that
it's in there anyway, Phoebe?
We have to assume that this
dust devil is part of the plan.
The cannon must be in a place where they
can still see well
enough to hit the target.
Also,
it has to be in an open
space where a cannon can fit,
but where it can't be seen from the sky.
This place is big enough, isn't it?
So then let's make it the clan's
secret base, what do you say?
Yeah!
So that has to be it.
It makes perfect sense to me.
Okay, hold on.
We'll leave the others a message
since you're headed this way.
Thanks, Usopp.
I'm going ahead to the tower.
Hey!
Wait, Vivi! Wait! Hurry! Right?
Well, look at that!
It's the princess!
We found her, boys!
Yeah, that was just too easy,
the signal led us right to her.
There are more members of
the Baroque Works Billions.
Oh, no!
We signaled the enemy too!
That smoke, Zuzab's signal,
he must have found it.
Okay, but why is the palace so far away?
Good, it's not far from here.
I wonder if that signal means
that they found the cannoneer.
They must have, let's go!
No!
Noisy attack!
Trimble at the power of my nails!
Come on, baby, let's go.
Hey, over there! Get him!
So it's you?
You can't get away.
You're mine.
How are you still alive?
No matter how many times I kill you,
you just keep coming back for more.
Well, answer me, brat.
How'd he do it?
How did he If you live and
come here, who is this boy?
It's Tryhat.
Tell me, just how many
times do you have to die?
There's something you still
need to return, Crocodile,
and I came here to get it back.
What is this thing I took?
Is it money?
Is it fame?
Or people's trust?
Their lives?
Is it rain?
I have taken all of those things.
So which is it that you want
me to give back, Straw Hat?
This land.
The land?
Really, you should know
better than that by now.
I have no intention of
relinquishing this country.
Why would I, when I'm going to
become its next king before long?
We came to this island
to save Vivi's country,
but then, when we got here, it was gone.
You stole her country!
I have to get to the rebel army.
I must persuade their leader to stop
all of this pointless bloodshed.
Up until a few short years ago,
it was a thriving city full of gardens
and palm trees and lush greenery.
Please, Vivi, you have to stop these
fools from tearing our country apart.
This is her country, and I'm
here to take it back from you.
Then what's wrong with that?
What's so very wrong about
not wanting to see people die?
Just being in this country one day and
taking a look around, even I can tell.
What this country needs
more than anything!
You think that putting
just your life on the
line is enough to stop
this from happening?
What do you mean?
I don't have anything else
I can put on the line.
Just me.
Well, you can at least try putting
all of our lives on the line together!
Aren't we friends, huh?
I will defeat you.
Take this country out of your evil hands.
And then, Vivi will smile again.
Threaten me as much as you like.
But without any water, you're nothing.
This is impossible.
He doesn't have any water,
so how can he kick me?
This is your fault, you monster!
This country would be peaceful
if it weren't for you!
It's heartbreaking, isn't it?
Their love for their kingdom
will be what destroys it.
I see you're using your blood.
Clever.
Blood can harden sand too, can't it?
First rain base, and then the royal
palace, and now, this underground temple.
You should be rewarded for your
insistence on challenging me.
Even after I've put you through hell
twice now, you keep coming back.
You're a pirate, Straw Hat.
You've certainly proven that in your
determination to defeat me, no matter the cost.
And I'll admit that you've
become an annoyingly
persistent opponent during
our three encounters.
Alright.
What's that?
A poisonous hook.
I see.
You seem to be a competent
pirate, I suppose.
So surely you must understand
that a duel between
pirates is always about two
people fighting for survival.
And when that's the case, there's
no such thing as playing dirty.
When the explosion happens in the square,
this place will most
likely crumble to dust.
This will be our final battle.
So let's settle this once and for all.
Smoke was coming from
this direction, wasn't it?
Or was it?
What? The Marines? Hey, look!
It's Roro Noa Saru!
Just great.
I didn't realize the Marines
were in this town now.
I don't have time for this.
Oh, damn it.
I guess I have no choice but
to deal with them quickly.
Why are you here in the
middle of the battlefield?
Yeah, what do you think you're doing here?
Well, I could say the same thing to you.
Hold it, Zoro!
Go that way.
If you head north at the next corner,
then you can reach the Palace Square.
Go back and turn right.
It's not this way.
Are you that stupid?
Stupid. Get out of here! Go!
What the...
How it just...
We have to run faster, BB!
I don't think I can, or something!
Don't let the princess get away!
Our promotions are on the...
Ah!
Ah! Ah!
Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah!
Ah!
Uh, thank you.
We're here to help you, not fight.
Go stop the explosion in the square, okay?
Now go, quickly.
Let's get going, Usopp.
Come on, hurry.
Right. Thank you.
Hurry, we have to hurry.
We've wasted a lot of time.
I don't know why they
helped us back there,
but if it weren't for the Marines,
we'd be a lot worse off now.
No, don't look at that.
We don't have time to help them.
If we don't stop the explosion, the
casualties would be a lot worse than that.
Right.
Crying about it isn't going to
stop the attack from happening.
In two minutes, we're either going
to beat them or we're going to die.
We still have time left. Yes.
And we're all helping you. Yes.
Right there.
Phoebe, who's up?
It's Nami and Tony.
What's going on?
The Marines just helped us out back there.
Were you able to find where the cannon is?
We haven't confirmed it yet, but
this is the only place it can be.
We must have passed it a bunch
of times before I realized it.
The cannon is up there.
I'm absolutely sure of it now.
The clock tower? I see.
From up there, he can get a
really good shot at the square.
We still need Pel to get here, though.
It's the only way to stop it.
Pel.
We don't have much time.
I could have sworn I saw the smoke coming
up from somewhere around this area.
Robot, Robot, Robot, Robot.
Did you see that?
I just shot down that big
bird with my Robot, Robot gun.
Quite impressive, huh?
I'm sorry.
Ohhhhhhhhhh
Hair!
Hiyori!
Come on, Pistol!
Oh, my God.
He's so strong.
Who in the world is he?
Crocodile made even our best
warriors look like children.
But now he's actually struggling.
You were skewered, buried
alive, and dried up.
You may have made it through all that,
but you won't escape this time, Straw Hat.
There's no hope for survival.
The game is over.
This poison will spread through you soon.
You know, crocodile, you
just don't understand.
I wonder what happened.
Well, I don't see him up there anywhere.
But I don't think there's
any way we can get to the
top of the tower in less than
a minute without any help?
Well, where are you?
Hurry,
we need you But now we're
going to have to get moving
without him We're gonna have
to climb all these stairs,
you guys ready?
Hey!
Huh?
Nami!
Hey, Vivi!
Sanji, what are you doing
all the way up there?
What do you think?
You left a message where
the smoke was, didn't you?
The message said go to the clock tower,
so I figured I'd better
head up here to meet you.
So what should I do?
Where's the cannoneer, anyway? The top!
He's at the top!
Go up from there and take him down!
Sanji?
Hey, where were you? I was
looking! Zoro? You're here, too?
What are you doing down there?
Funny, I was gonna ask you the same thing!
It was the Marines!
I kept saying, go north, go north!
So I just kept going north
till I got all the way up here!
North and up aren't the same thing!
Anyway, good job, you two!
Now just keep on going up from there
and destroy the clock tower, okay?
No way!
They can't get inside the clock
tower from where they are now.
You see, there are only two ways in.
The back stairs on the first
floor and from the sky.
That's why we need Pell!
But can't Zoro just go ahead and
destroy the wall or something?
We can't risk that.
It could make the cannonball explode
even earlier for all we know.
We have no choice but to take the stairs.
No, wait, Vivi!
I think I have a better plan!
So, Mr. Seven,
according to what the boss told us,
this is going to be our final
mission for Baroque Works!
Robot!
That's right, Miss Father's Day!
According to the plan, we have
just 30 seconds left to go.
Who are they? Mr.
Seven and Miss Father's Day.